Good afternoon. - Good afternoon.
Hello.
This is Nao Tomisato, Nogizaka46 5th term
I'm Haruka Kuromi, a 4th term
And this is Satsuki Sugawara.
I'm a 5th term.
I'm now a 4th term.
I'm counting on you.
Please.
Where are we today?
Where are we?
How are we doing?
What do you think?
Hey, girl.
Naochan's water
We're at Women's College.
Yes, sir.
Yes, ma'am.
We are having a Golden Festival
We're having a school festival.
I'd like to sneak in with the three of us!
I'm too excited!
It's a rare event, isn't it?
That's for sure.
It's not so rare.
I'm so excited!
You want to go now?
I'd like to go.
Hi, I'm 46 and I'd like to throw it.
I'm 46, and I'm looking forward to meeting you.
First of all, may I ask why you applied?
We've had a lot of requests from current students to apply for this year's contest.
We are very happy that you are interested in coming to our school.
Thank you very much for your application.
Thank you very much.
This is a pamphlet.
It's very cute.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad you like it.
Amazing! So cute!
Let's have fun watching this!
It's so much fun!
Nice to meet you!
So many flyers!
It's like a school festival!
It's a school festival!
Oh, my gosh!
Awesome, awesome, awesome!
Look at this! Dos Equis steak.
Oh, that looks so good!
There's so much to choose from!
What to choose?
Oh, my God.
What?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Great, great, great, great.
Sudden animal.
So cool!
They're takoyaki. - What?
What? Look.
It's the size of a takoyaki.
You just go ahead and do it.
What? Me?
Me?
I want to do it.
You want out?
I want to get out. I want to get out.
Can I ask you not to answer?
What?
Thank you so much.
I'm going to be in Oka's classroom.
There's such a cool cast.
It's great.
And you can take Chakki pictures with them.
That's great.
You should do it.
It's like pushing and looking for something.
I'll see you later.
Thank you so much!
Takoyaki at the Old Dome.
What are you doing?
That's great. - That's great.
Yumiki's doing it.
Mr. Yumiki?
Are you doing it, Ms. Yumiki?
Mr. Yumiki's doing it.
I'm so disappointed.
I want some takoyaki.
I'll be back in a minute.
Thank you.
Which one do you like?
Honjiru.
How do you like it?
It's delicious.
Smells good.
It's a little cold now, isn't it?
Beef skewers look delicious!
Some of the skewers are amazing!
Look at the beef skewers!
Beef skewers!
They're wearing faces!
Furisa and Nao.
Sato Sugawara.
They really noticed.
That's so cool!
So cool!
The inside of an octopus is tiny.
Thank you so much.
What do we do now?
You want some soup?
Beef skewer.
What should we do?
Would you like a skewer?
I feel like it.
I'll have some.
Let's eat
Beef skewer.
Thank you very much.
Beef skewer, please.
How many skewers?
One for now.
Do you want to share?
We'd like to eat a variety.
What should we do?
What do you think, senpai?
Let's share one.
Let's do that for now.
I'm going to eat one from the start.
It's so good!
Thank you so much!
Looks delicious.
Amazing.
Please enjoy the rest of the meal.
Thank you very much.
After you.
Me first?
Looks delicious.
Bon appétit.
How is it?
It's delicious.
It's so good.
It's really good.
It's good.
It's delicious.
It's so rare to eat something like this without a mask.
It's so rare. I'm so happy.
It's so cute.
How is it? Hi, Sonny.
Delicious.
Rope cake.
It's like we're boyfriend and girlfriend.
What do you think?
I'm through.
It's so good!
So soft!
It's so soft.
It's so soft!
Wonderfully delicious.
Did you find anything?
Personally, I think of the school festival in terms of candy butters.
Let's eat butter candy.
I want some.
Can I have a butter candy?
Let's eat it!
What flavor would you like?
Normal strawberry, melon, lemon-orange.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know.
What flavor do you want?
What do you recommend?
I recommend strawberry.
Okay, strawberry.
I'll buy strawberry cotton candy.
Just out of the corner of your eye, right?
Kuromi's strawberry color.
That's right.
I colored it strawberry because I knew you'd eat strawberries.
Really?
Genius.
Thank you.
I thought so.
Oh, my God.
Here it comes.
Good luck with the rice cakes.
Thank you.
I got your rice cakes.
Thank you very much.
This way please.
This way.
What's this?
It's raining again.
Try my amen.
Wow.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
Bon appétit.
Just a little bit.
It melted in an instant.
Yummy, sweet, so sweet.
Strawberries?
They're really strawberries.
Look at his mouth!
It's so tiny.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're a strawberry, aren't you, Kurumi?
Just because we're in the same class doesn't mean I'm less of a friend.
I didn't get a good shot.
I couldn't get a good shot.
Open your mouth.
Okay.
Ha-ha-ha.
Open your mouth.
I'll take a close-up.
That's good.
It was about five times as much as mine.
It's hard work.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Delicious.
I'm glad you liked it.
You look good with cotton candy.
Really?
It's like a fashion statement.
I'll give you a big bowl of cotton candy.
It's not gonna fit in your mouth.
He's so cute.
It's cute.
Can you do it?
Yes!
Gomogo.
NO?
It was gone in an instant.
He got the one I just did.
Thank you for the food.
thanks for dinner.
so what do we do now?
Can I get you anything? I'm thirsty.
Sure.
I just saw a sign that said "Kee-chan Cafe".
There's a character named Kee-chan.
Shall we go?
She's a fairy who lives in Chanomizu University.
A fairy?
She's a character.
She's always saying "Nano".
Nano?
I'll go by "nano" from now on.
I'm thirsty.
Mixing them together makes me sick.
What's going on?
Mochi? When it's full of rice cakes...
Yay!
It's like a mansion.
A hall.
Wow.
This way?
Let's go this way.
It looks like it's going this way.
Oh, there it is.
There it is. 124.
Kii-chan Cafe Kobo!
There's hojicha latte and matcha latte.
Which one do you want?
I'll have a hojicha latte.
Then I'll have a matcha latte.
Hojicha and matcha.
Of course.
Thank you very much.
Okay.
I like you to eat a lot.
A big bite
Yay, yay, yay
Yay, yay, yay, it's starting
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes, matcha latte
Yes, thank you!
It's so cute!
Look at this.
Wow.
So cute!
What kind of facial expression do you want, Sacha?
Oh, it's a heart!
A heart!
Thank you very much.
Popular with the girls? You're a hit with the ladies.
I'm popular.
Everyone is different.
He's cute.
I'm at the cafe!
I'm here!
Kin-chan Cafe!
Cheers!
Isn't this the kind of toast you're supposed to make?
It's so hot!
Hot!
It's hot, but it's delicious.
I'm sorry I didn't drink it, but it's a little bit closed.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's so rich and delicious, Michiko.
Smells good.
Take it easy. It might be hot.
It's delicious. It's so creamy.
But it's so good. I don't usually drink hot tea.
I don't usually drink hot, even when it's cold.
I see. It's good hot too. I haven't had a drop yet.
I haven't had a drop yet.
It's so hot, but it's a café.
Loveoo...
Wow!
Wow.
Oh, my God.
Here it comes.
How is it?
Delicious! It's a little bitter.
But I'm 18 now, so I can handle it.
You're all grown up now, aren't you?
I'm 18, so I can do it.
I can do it.
It's delicious.
Thank you very much.
There's a lot of stuff here.
What do you want to go next?
Cheese balls.
We have cheese balls.
We've got college potatoes, the members' favorite.
Cheese and sweet potato cakes...
Yes, ma'am.
Pancake churros.
Oh, that looks delicious.
There are so many!
What is this?
Frankfurters.
It's a dance stage.
You can eat frankfurters here.
Three or four members and a manager are selling frankfurters.
They are selling frankfurters.
It says they're going to perform on the dance stage.
Do you want to go?
Shall we go?
Let's go.
There seems to be a lot of things to do.
I want to do something like this...
I want to do something like this.
voodoo... like this... like this...
Eсли
I feel great!
I can't eat for the rest of my life.
What do you mean? You can eat your life?
Oh, my God.
Oh, sweet potato cakes.
Do you want a sweet potato cake?
I want a taro cake.
Want some?
Do you want a taro cake?
Sure.
You want some?
I don't know. Cheese balls.
Which one do you want?
Which one do you like better?
You want to go take a look?
They have cheese balls.
It says "sticky" on it.
Wait, graduate school, too.
You have grad school, too.
I'm only sleeping here.
Wait a minute, there's too much to eat
Poku-poku cheese balls!
2 boobar juices, let's eat...
I'm so fancy!
clairement... you want to do a little bit of that... tomorrow 4...
Thank you very much...
You can have 60 iphones.
I'm just holding it.
I'm going to stretch the cheese. It might be hot. It's ok.
Who wants some?
How is it?
Yum!
Good?
It's good.
Oh, it's good, it's good, it's good.
Look at that.
You're so cute.
It's good. - It's good.
Thank you. Thank you.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Is it good?
It's amazing.
What?
It's delicious. The sweet honey and the sesame seeds give it a nice kick.
Who wants some?
I want some.
Dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah.
I got a sticky mess.
Hot.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go, let's go.
What was that?
Dance?
Tic-tac-toe?
Thank you very much.
He's cute.
Shall we take a look?
It's like she's doing a spin dance or something.
I wonder where it is.
There it is.
What's with the dark outfit?
Oh, I wonder if it's that.
I wonder if it's that one.
Not here?
You guys are so cute.
Is it that one?
So cute.
What do you want me to do?
What should I say?
I don't know.
It's some kind of idol.
What's it called?
Is it a dance troupe? That's a better question.
Okay.
Okay, I'll follow up with you in a bit.
Yes, please.
There he is.
Where am I supposed to put my clothes?
I'm coming.
So, is this a dance club?
Yes, sir.
Oh, my God.
You're so cute.
Hello.
May I have one?
Thank you very much.
Are you in a dance club or something?
Yes, an idol dance club.
Yes.
I know Nogizaka.
With the screen? Of course.
I was wondering if I could ask you a few questions.
I was wondering what you do.
Usually we practice Japanese female idol dances
We're practicing Japanese pop idol dances.
I see.
We have a stage.
Yay!
Amazing.
Do you do any Mizusaka songs?
Garururu!
By the way, can I see Garururu?
It's black!
That's great!
It's a collaboration with the original.
Can I see it?
Yes!
Thank you so much.
So cute!
Here you go, ladies and gentlemen.
How did you learn that?
I don't know.
I took a bunch of videos from singing shows and stuff.
I'm so happy!
That's great!
Thank you very much.
What do you want to do? How do you want to do it?
Rusty, this is it.
Oh, that's it.
First person to turn, second person to turn.
"First to turn, second to turn, and third to turn.
And the one who goes around the back.
I see.
Wow, they're all divided up.
That's great. That's great. - Yeah.
Let's go in the gap.
Okay, okay.
Yes, yes. I'm so embarrassed.
I've done this so many times, I'm getting nervous.
Let's start with the girls. - Right. It's easier if we're going for it.
Ready?
The girls sing "One, Two, Three
They fall in love and graduate
Girls' Blue
Fall in love with him
Together Always
I want to be
He'll be happy to see me
I have to be wronged, car
me 1 grasp Seafaree
I want to be in this sea none
Someday, I'll be fine.
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah.
Oh, even though my hands are doing this.
It's going to be the first boil.
Will you go sometime?
Just one more time.
Can I start on the 5th?
Can I do it from the 5th?
Here.
OK OK
Hello, hello, hello.
Five. Six. Seven.
Five.
I'll keep Girls Roo in my heart until I remember this day
Ta-da!
Den! Deng deng deng deng!
How did you make it this far?
I'm so nervous!
I was more nervous than at a normal concert.
Well, enjoy!
I was more nervous than at a normal show.
It's so much fun!
Amazing Yuka!
Thank you so much!
That was awesome!
Please support us!
Thank you! Please support me!
It really looks like a VLOG!
I don't know how to drink it right.
We are in the middle of a vaccine that you can enjoy today!
Thank you.
I think he's lying.
What's wrong?
Yes, sir! We've come full circle.
Yes, sir!
How was it?
It was so much fun!
It was a lot of fun.
It's not often you get a chance to go to a college...
It's not often you get a chance to go to a college... it's the first time I've ever been to one.
We ate delicious food and had a lot of fun. I'm sure there are a lot of fans who support the Kesaka in various places around the country.
I'm sure there are a lot of fans all over the country, or at least in various places, who support the hairy hill.
Thank you very much.